http://www.rapplaw.com/privacy-policy#disclaimer

Skip to content
Meet Our AttorneysPractice Areas & FAQsFree Case ReviewIn The NewsReviews
English Español
Search for:
Meet Our AttorneysPractice Areas & FAQsFree Case ReviewIn The NewsReviews
Search for:
Call our law firm today! Consult with the partners for FREE.
800-734-9445Our Locations:Islandia Office: 1355 Motor Parkway Islandia, NY 11749Directions: Google MapsManhattan Office: 570 Lexington Ave. New York, NY 10022 Directions: Google Maps
Privacy PolicyRGLZ Law_MM2020-06-22T15:05:48-04:00
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy applies to information collected online from users of this website. In this policy, you can learn what kind of information we collect, when and how we might use that information, how we protect the information, and the choices you have with respect to your personal information.
What personal information is collected through this website and how is it used?
We collect information about our users in three ways: directly from the user, from our Web server logs and through cookies. We use the information primarily to provide you with a personalized Internet experience that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you. We don’t share any of the information you provide with others, unless we say so in this Privacy Policy, or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.
User-supplied information: If you fill out the contact form on this website, we will ask you to provide some personal information (such as e-mail address, name, phone number and state). We only require that you provide an e-mail address on the contact form. Further, if chat is available through this site, you may be asked to provide information if you participate in an online chat. Please do not submit any confidential, proprietary or sensitive personally identifiable information (e.g. Social Security Number; date of birth; drivers license number; or credit card, bank account or other financial information) (collectively, “Sensitive Information”). If you submit any Sensitive Information, you do so at your own risk and we will not be liable to you or responsible for consequences of your submission.
Information that you provide to us through the contact form or an online chat will be used so that we may respond to your inquiry. We may also use information you provide to us to communicate with you in the future. If you do not wish to receive such communications, you may opt out (unsubscribe) as described below.
Web server logs: When you visit our website, we may track information about your visit and store that information in web server logs, which are records of the activities on our sites. The servers automatically capture and save the information electronically.
Examples of the information we may collect include:
your unique Internet protocol address;
the name of your unique Internet service provider;
the town/city, county/state and country from which you access our website;
the kind of browser or computer you use;
the number of links you click within the site;
the date and time of your visit;
the web page from which you arrived to our site;
the pages you viewed on the site; and
certain searches/queries that you conducted via our website(s).
The information we collect in web server logs helps us administer the site, analyze its usage, protect the website and its content from inappropriate use and improve the user’s experience.
Cookies: In order to offer and provide a customized and personal service, our websites and applications may use cookies to store and help track information about you. Cookies are simply small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies to help remind us who you are and to help you navigate our sites during your visits. Cookies allow us to save passwords and preferences for you so you won’t have to re-enter them each time you visit.
The use of cookies is relatively standard. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. However, if you prefer, you can set your browser to either notify you when you receive a cookie, or to refuse to accept cookies. You should understand that some features of many sites may not function properly if you don’t accept cookies.
How is personal information protected?
We take certain appropriate security measures to help protect your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized persons will always be unable to defeat our security measures.
Who has access to the information?
We will not sell, rent, or lease mailing lists or other user data to others, and we will not make your personal information available to any unaffiliated parties, except as follows:
to agents, website vendors and/or contractors who may use it on our behalf or in connection with their relationship with us;
if we are unable to assist with your matter, but know an unaffiliated attorney or firm that may be able to help you, we may refer you and share information you provided us with that party; and as required by law, in a matter of public safety or policy, as needed in connection with the transfer of our business assets (for example, if we are acquired by another firm or if we are liquidated during bankruptcy proceedings), or if we believe in good faith that sharing the data is necessary to protect our rights or property.
How can I correct, amend or delete my personal information and/or opt out of future communications?
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. Contact us by phone 631-293-2300 , contact form or our mailing address located at the bottom of our website at any time to:
see what data we have about you, if any;
change/correct any data we have about you;
ask us to delete any data we have about you; and/or opt out of future communications from us.
If you have any additional questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us via the phone number, contact form or mailing address listed on this website. If our information practices change in a significant way, we will post the policy changes here.
Effective January 1, 2020 Attorney Advertising Disclaimer:
No Attorney Client Relationship without signed agreement
Viewing this website does not form an attorney/client relationship between you and the attorneys of Rappaport, Glass, Levine & Zullo LLP. No attorney/client relationship occurs unless and until you sign an agreement confirming the nature and scope of representation.
Not Legal Advice
This website is for informational purposes only and does not contain legal advice. Please do not act or refrain from acting based on anything you read on this site.
Confidentiality
No website is entirely secure, so please be cautious information provided through the contact form or email. Do not assume confidentiality exists in anything you send through this website or email, until an attorney/client relationship is formed through completion of a fee agreement.
Advertising
Attorney websites, such as this one, are considered attorney advertising.
No prior result in a case guarantees a future result that is the same. Each case we handle is individual with different facts and therefore every case is different. We cannot guarantee any specific result in your case.
Contact UsPersonal InjuryPersonal Injury OverviewAmputationsBrain InjuriesBurns And DisfigurementChild Abuse And MolestationDefective ProductsDrunk Driving Accident VictimsEye Injuries And Vision LossKnee And Leg InjuriesLegal And Professional MalpracticeMunicipal LiabilityShoulder InjuriesSpinal Cord InjuriesWrongful Death ClaimsNew York Car AccidentsNew York Car Accidents OverviewDistracted DrivingHead-on CollisionsJackknife AccidentsOverloaded TrucksRear-end CollisionsRollover AccidentsTruck AccidentsMedical MalpracticeMedical Malpractice OverviewBirth InjuriesBirth Injury OverviewCerebral PalsyErb’s PalsyFailure To Recognize Signs Of Fetal DistressShoulder DystociaUterine Rupture & C-SectionDoctor ErrorsAnesthesia ErrorsCataract Surgery InjuriesEmergency Room ErrorsGastric Bypass Surgery InjuriesMedication ErrorsSurgical ErrorsDefective Medical EquipmentSt. Jude ICD / CRT-D DevicesDiagnostic ErrorsDelayed Diagnosis Of CancerFailure To DiagnoseFailure To Diagnose A Heart AttackFailure To Properly Read X-Rays And MammogramsMisdiagnosisNegligent MalpracticeFatal Medical MalpracticeNewborn Respiratory Distress SyndromePediatric MalpracticeDiabetic AmputationsNursing Home InjuriesNursing Home Injuries OverviewNursing Home Wrongful DeathAbuseAlzheimer’s Patient AbuseMedication Abuse And NegligenceMental And Emotional AbusePhysical AbusePhysical And Chemical RestraintsSexual AssaultSuspicious InjuriesNegligenceBed SoresFailure To Follow Care PlansFailure To MonitorFallsInadequate StaffingMalnutrition And DehydrationStaph InfectionsWandering Off/elopementConstruction AccidentsConstruction Accidents OverviewScaffold And Ladder AccidentsExcavation And Demolition AccidentsDitch AccidentsTool And Machinery AccidentsFaulty Breathing ApparatusElectrical Accidents And InjuriesInjuries Caused By Falling ObjectsRoofing AccidentsNew York’s Scaffold Law: A Legal Safety Net For New York’s Construction WorkersSlip And Fall & Premises LiabilitySlip And Fall/Premises Liability OverviewDog Bites And AttacksElevator AccidentsNegligent SecurityStair AccidentsUnsecured Construction AreaMotorcycle AccidentsMotorcycle Accidents OverviewFatal Motorcycle AccidentsPedestrian AccidentsPedestrian Accidents OverviewBicycle AccidentsBad Faith
Close Sliding Bar Area
Coronavirus is changing the way the NYS legal system operates. We are monitoring those changes to ensure that the interests of our clients are fully protected.
While the spread of coronavirus in New York State has declined, we want to reassure our clients that we are taking every precaution necessary to adhere to the guidelines in helping to stop the spread  of the virus.  You will notice these changes when you enter our building.
We are now also offering virtual conferencing in addition to in person meetings.  If you would like to keep up with the latest news and updates please visit : https://www.rglzlaw.com/covid-19-ny
